ANTHONY YONTA - アンソニー ヨンタ

1248 WALLACE STREET, RICHMOND, VA 23220

H: 804-317-8646 | atischillin@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Seasoned I.T. professional with more than 12 years of experience in fast-paced client-oriented team environments. Excellent communication and problem-solving skills. Track record of achieving exceptional results for clients and working with my peers to increase overall team performance. My personal goals are to increase in general I.T. knowledge in networking, security, full stack development and to learn another programming language.

SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- Bootstrap
- React.js
- MongoDB / MySQL
- Git / Github Branching
- Hardware install / server racks / full computer construction and repair

- JavaScript / jQuery /Java
- Express.js
- Node.js
- Command Line
- Windows 7, 10 and office suite

EXPERIENCE

HUNTON ANDREWS KURTH LLP

IT Support Ctr Coordinator | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | February 2014 - Current

- Provided onsite, remote technical support, and coaching for firm supported applications and services such as Office 2010 2016, Adobe acrobat, Nuance PDF, iManage, and Litera products.
- Managed client accounts, passwords, network access, and application installations using Active Directory and System Center Configuration Manager.
- Deployed and configured firm software to mobile devices using AirWatch.
- Experienced in Service Now ticketing environment to accurately document and escalate incidents and requests in a timely manner.
- Create, maintain, and enter information into our internal I.T.
- Knowledge base for fixes / resolutions, general documentation and SOP.

- Collaborated with neighboring teams on multiple projects to develop a greater understanding
 of their roles and responsibilities and to reduce turn-around time.
- Organized, inventoried, and managed firm assets and assisted with hardware deployments.
- Traveled to support multiple out-of-state office consolidations and hardware setups.

GEED SQUAD ADVANCED, BEST BUY

Repair Agent | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | February 2014 - August 2016

- Accurate interpenetrate client description of the problem to find accurate solutions.
- Diagnose, troubleshoot and repair software and operating systems on client personal Desktop and laptops.
- Assembled, maintained, and repaired system hardware.
- Held accountable for accurate notes and client communications.
- Fully Assembled, maintained, and repaired system hardware.

GEEK SQUAD DEPUTY OF COUNTER INTELLIGENCE, BEST BUY

Manager | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | August 2009 - February 2014

- Responsible for all operations of the in-store Geek Squad Businesses and Brand representation.
- Develop Department Business Plan and execution including Car Audio install bay.
- Hiring, training, scheduling and development of over 20 employees.
- Responsible for all Client interactions, including corporate complaints.
- Managed and accountable for paperwork and legal documentation regarding the paid for services.
- Perform hardware and software repair/upgrades, virus removals, network repair and client consulting.
- Lead and develop district wide training and best practices.

SHOCKOE PROPERTIES LLC

Maintenance Technician | Richmond, United States, VA, United States | June 2006 - August 2011

- Oversee all operations concerning the common areas of the building.
- Supervise cleanliness and security of the buildings.
- Daily interfacing with tenants and owners.
- Scheduling and supervising contractors, vendors and construction.
- Generated information for management regarding building efficiency regarding cost of repairs, overall maintenance, construction and upgrades.

JOHN TYLER COMMUNITY COLLEGE - MIDLOTHIAN CAMPUS

Math and English Tutor | VA, United States | August 2005 - June 2006

- Students taking freshman and sophomore college level Math and English.
- Scheduled appointments, fielded phone calls and filed paperwork.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE: FULL STACK MERN WEB DEVELOPTMENT

University of Richmond

Richmond, VA, United States | 2020

Full Stack MERN Web Developmental: Mongo DB, Express JS, React JS/ Redux and Node JS. Among these technologies Mongo DB is a database system, Node JS is a back-end runtime environment, Express JS is a back-end web framework and React is a front-end framework.

Personal Study in math Virginia Commonwealth University VA, United States | 2016

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE

John Tyler Community College Richmond, VA, United States | 2009

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS

John Tyler Community College VA, United States | 2009

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Midlothian High School

VA, United States | 2005